filma24-al.com 2015-09-30

# Privacy Policy

****Personal Information**  
**[Filma24-Al.com](http://www.filma24-al.com/)**** is committed to protecting your privacy online.   
We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our web site.

**IP address and logging**  
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns   
(how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).

**Credit card details**

Filma24-AL.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Filma24-AL.com.

**External Sites.**

Filma24-AL.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites.   
You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information   
(not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to   
provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to   
know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here

**Cookies**  
Some ads displayed may come from our servers. Ads loading from our servers may also contain cookies, the purpose of these cookies   
is just to introduce and select the proper advertisements to be shown for your interests. We only have access to information of   
visiting frequencies of our visitors from cookies you might receive while viewing ads from our servers.   
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Filma24-AL.com to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc).  
Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Filma24-AL.com does not use cookies to collect personal information.   
Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Filma24-AL.com   
and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.   
In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Filma24-AL.com   
have separate data and privacy practices independent of us,   
and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. 

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

**Copyright** © 2013 - 2015 | **Filma24-Al.com** \- Filma dhe Seriale HD
